Guide to the Transgender Erotic Pulp Fiction Collection from the Series Crossdressed
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Transgender erotic pulp fiction collection from the series Crossdressed
1990-1996
Bailey 17
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
1
49 v.; 17 cm.
Erotic pulp fiction related to male cross-dressing, including forced feminization.
Bailey, Laura E., 1951-
Star Distributors, Ltd
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Scope and Contents
Erotic pulp fiction related to male cross-dressing, including forced feminization.
Individual titles (see accompanying list) taken from cover.
All individual titles paperbound.
Cross-dressers -- Fiction; Cross-dressing -- Fiction; Transgender people -- Fiction; Sexual dominance and submission -- Fiction; Sex -- Fiction; Erotic stories; Erotica -- New York (State) -- New York -- 20th Century; LGBTQ resource; Bailey, Laura E., 1951- -- Ownership
- Crossdressed
  - Nick, c1990; CD_101_ (Box 101-135)
    Scope and Contents
    Stamp on top edge: MAP MAP MAP
  - Dreamer, c1990; CD_102_ (Box 101-135)
  - TV frat house, c1990; CD_103_ (Box 101-135)
  - TV nympho, c1990; first printing 1985; CD_104_ (Box 101-135)
  - The in-laws, c1991; CD_105_ (Box 101-135)
  - Tim/Tami, c1991; CD_106_ (Box 101-135)
  - Alan learns the ropes, c1991; CD_107_ (Box 101-135)
  - TV nun, c1991; first printing 1988; CD_108_ (Box 101-135)
  - Preacher's new dress, c1992; CD_110_ (Box 101-135)
    Stamp on top edge: 10
  - Harry, Barry Jill, c1992; first printing 1988; CD_112_ (Box 101-135)
  - Frills, c1992; CD_113_ (Box 101-135)
    "Stamp on top edge: 2.75 [?] Stamp on bottom edge: Model Dist. Front cover detached"
  - She-male fantasy, c1992; CD_114_ (Box 101-135)
  - Lace bondage, c1992, c1989; CD_115_ (Box 101-135)
    Front cover detached
  - Forced into panties, c1992, c1989; CD_116_ (Box 101-135)
  - Madame's TV slave, c1993; CD_117_ (Box 101-135)
  - Frilly stud, c1993; CD_118_ (Box 101-135)
    Stamp on bottom edge: Model Dist.
  - Forced into crossdressing, c1993; CD_119_ (Box 101-135)
  - Satin beefcake, c1993; CD_120_ (Box 101-135)
  - Cocks in white satin, c1994; first printing 1987; CD_121_ (Box 101-135)
    Stamp on bottom edge: SODI
  - Inside Peter's panties, c1994; first printing 1987; CD_122_ (Box 101-135)
  - His Victorian secret, c1994; first printing 1990; CD_123_ (Box 101-135)
  - She had balls, c1994; previously printed 1986, 1990; CD_124_ (Box 101-135)
  - Sissy jock, c1994; first printing 1985 under title "Jock in lace"; reprinted 1990; CD_125_ (Box 101-135)
  - Stud with a difference, c1994; first printing 1989 under title "Frilly stud"; CD_126_ (Box 101-135)
    Inventory (?) label on front cover: 3/05/95 424605
  - Tim's secret, c1994; first printing 1992 under title "Tracy"; CD_127_ (Box 101-135)
    Barcode price label on front cover: Rtn. By 3/12/95 $4.95
  - He's a she!, c1994; first printing 1989 under title "A guy with tits"; reprinted 1991; CD_128_ (Box 101-135)
  - Nikki, c1994; CD_132_ (Box 101-135)
  - Teen swinger, c1995; first printing 1985; CD_134_ (Box 101-135)
  - Forced she-male, c1995; first printing 1980; CD_135_ (Box 101-135)
    Stamp on top edge: Model Dist.
  - Shamed schoolboy, c1995; first printing 1983; CD_136_ (Box 136-156)
  - Movie star in lace, c1995; first printing 1985; CD_137_ (Box 136-156)
  - Serving she-male, c1995; first printing 1990; CD_138_ (Box 136-156)
    Stamp on bottom edge: CVD
  - The banker had a secret, c1995; first printing 1981; CD_139_ (Box 136-156)
  - Drag race, c1995; first printing 1987; reprinted 1990; CD_140_ (Box 136-156)
  - Macho maid, c1995; CD_141_ (Box 136-156)
  - Sonny boy-girl, c1995; CD_143_ (Box 136-156)
  - She-male tease, c1995; CD_144_ (Box 136-156)
    Stamp on top edge: CVD
  - Satin bound, c1995; CD_145_ (Box 136-156)
  - Officer in training bra, c1995; CD_146_ (Box 136-156)
  - Garter belted guy, c1995; CD_147_ (Box 136-156)
  - Her panty slave, c1995; CD_148_ (Box 136-156)
  - Executive sweet, c1996; CD_149_ (Box 136-156)
  - Charlie's pink panties, c1996; CD_150_ (Box 136-156)
    Inventory (?) label on back cover: 2 08
  - Bulging black lace, c1996; CD_151_ (Box 136-156)
  - One man's negligee, c1996; CD_152_ (Box 136-156)
    "Stamp on bottom edge: MAP MAP MAP Inventory (?) label on back cover: 9607"
  - Coaching Bobby, c1996; CD_153_ (Box 136-156)
  - Protruding panties, c1996; CD_154_ (Box 136-156)
  - Hide that bulge!, c1996; CD_155_ (Box 136-156)
  - Satin threesome, c1996; CD_156_ (Box 136-156)
    Stamp on top edge: 22